eurodownload.com 2006-12-10

# Download - Software, freeware, shareware

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy which lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. The following policies are only in effect for the Web pages, newsletters and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by Euro Download.com. 

**What information are you collecting and how are you collecting it?**

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers known as the "Internet Protocol" IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any Web Site within the Euro Download.com, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name, IP address, access times, referring web sites, and browser type. This information reveals nothing personal about you. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, and to investigate misuse of the Euro Download.com, its users, or to cooperate with law enforcement. We do not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals. Our Web servers do not record e-mail addresses of the visitors. 

**What are cookies?**

When using our Site, Euro Download.com or its advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of Euro Download.com Web Site you have visited, personalized or customized, so the next time you visit those pages may be readily accessible. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. We, and our advertisers, may use this information to better personalize the content and promotions that you see on our Site. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to notify you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other Web sites will not work as intended. 

**How do you use single-pixel gifs?**

Euro Download.com and its advertisers may use single-pixel gif images, sometimes referred to as web bugs or web beacons, to count Web page accesses and gather some general statistical information. Euro Download.com does not gather personal information through the use of these images. Our advertisers may use single-pixel gifs that can track personal information from cookies that may have been previously placed on a user's computer by an advertiser. 

**What information do you collect when I register for something?**

Euro Download.com offers access to services that are free but that require registration. We will use your registration contact information to send notification of Euro Download.com products and services by e-mail and/or postal mail. We also may share that information with our clients. Our clients may send you promotional material that is related to the topic of the service for which you registered unless you have chosen not to receive it. **Euro Download.com reserves the right to send to our registered members email notices and announcements that may be of interest to Euro Download.com users. TO NOT RECEIVE ANY COMMUNICATION FROM EURODOWNLOAD.COM, MEMBERS SHOULD REQUEST THAT THEIR REGISTRATION BE CANCELLED AND AGREE NOT TO USE ANY FREE EURODOWNLOAD.COM SERVICES.**

**What other information do you request?**

We will most likely also request your e-mail address or mailing address and other personal information for the purposes of providing additional services (for example, subscriptions to e-mail newsletters, announcement lists or information about seminars). Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested. We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy that means that we do not intend to sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent. 

We may from time to time send e-mail announcing new Euro Download.com products and services. By using services on Euro Download.com Web Site, you are agreeing we can send you this email. If you choose to supply your postal address in an online form, you may receive mailings from other third party companies. 

**Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties?**

Euro Download.com will disclose personal information and/or an IP address, when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: 

Euro Download.com uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. Euro Download.com reserves the right to transfer all such information in connection with the sale of all or part of Euro Download.com's capital stock or assets. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. We are not responsible for such third party privacy policies or how they treat information about their users 

**Opt-in announcement List Privacy Policy**

As an added benefit to the visitors of the Euro Download.com site, we have a relationship with PostMasterDirect, an independent third party company that sends e-mail announcements to individuals who request to receive them. When you register you are given the opportunity to also receive announcement lists from PostmasterDirect. Whether you want to receive these announcement lists is your choice; you should only receive those lists you affirmatively choose to. If you choose to receive a specific announcement list, you will receive commercial messages that are related to the topic of the list from independent third parties that have contracted with Euro Download.com and/or PostMasterDirect to send messages to the list. Personally identifiable information will not be used by Euro Download.com or PostMasterDirect for any purposes other than to deliver the e-mail announcements. You may stop the arrival of these announcement lists at any time by removing your e-mail address from the list by forwarding the announcement list to deleteall@postmasterdirect.com, or by following the instructions on the e-mails you receive. 

**What else should I know about my privacy when online?**

The Euro Download.com site contains many hyperlinks to other Web sites and from Affiliate Web sites. The Euro Download.com Web Sites also contain advertisements of third parties. Euro Download.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites or advertisers. Euro Download.com does not share any of the individual personal information you provide to us with the Web sites to which Euro Download.com links. 

**Your Consent to This Agreement**  
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by Euro Download.com and agree to receive communications from Euro Download.com as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

Please send any questions about Euro Download.com's Privacy Policy here: contact us.
